{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/51622876","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622876","name":"Leila Restaurant LLC","address":"1249 Griswold","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Samy Eid","licenseNumber":"243180","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"150","coords":"-83.04999,42.33325","geojson":{"id":"51622876","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.049988923,42.333251182]},"properties":{"name":"Leila Restaurant LLC","owner":"Samy Eid","address":"1249 Griswold","zipcode":"48226","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"243180","establishmentid":"51622876","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"150","most_recent_license_date":null}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","address":"1215 Griswold","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4214","name":"St. Aloysius","address":"1234  Washington Blvd.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4641","name":"St. Aloysius Church-Neighbor Hood Servic","address":"1234 Washington","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51623592","name":"SpkrBox","address":"200 Grand River","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51622773","name":"Clementina Cocina & Libaciones- Mobile","address":"150 State St.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51622771","name":"Clementina Cocina & Libaciones- Bar","address":"150 State St.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51622763","name":"Cannelle Detroit LLC","address":"45 Grand River W.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4518","name":"Urban Bean Company","address":"1405 Griswold","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"1626","name":"Detroit Pizza","address":"1250 Griswold","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5155","name":"Shopper's Lounge DBA Queens Bar","address":"35 Grand River E.","zipcode":"48226"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"52654","inspectionDate":"2020-09-03T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"49418","inspectionDate":"2019-10-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"door(s)","problemDescription":"Not sealed to prevent pest entry","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Openings","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-101.19","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT that are exposed to splash, spillage, or other FOOD soiling or that require frequent cleaning shall be constructed of a CORROSION-RESISTANT, nonabsorbent, and SMOOTH material.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"BAR ( FIRST FLOOR)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to adjoining","subProblem":"Wall(s)","location":"BASEMENT","subLocation":"Mop sink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to adjoining","subProblem":"Wall(s)","location":"BASEMENT (BAR)","subLocation":"Ice bin","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Seal to wall/equipment to facilitate cleaning."},{"violationCode":"5-501.11","violationDescription":"An outdoor storage surface for REFUSE, recyclables, and returnable's shall be constructed of nonabsorbent material such as concrete or asphalt and shall be SMOOTH, durable, and sloped to drain.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over","subProblem":"Gravel","location":"OUTSIDE PREMISES","subLocation":"Dumpster(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to adjoining","subProblem":"Wall(s)","location":"BAR ( FIRST FLOOR)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"","location":"BAR ( FIRST FLOOR)","subLocation":"Handsink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"","location":"BASEMENT (BAR)","subLocation":"Handsink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-13T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622876"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}